芝加哥的暴力行为已经蔓延到当选的官员
The violence in Chicago has now touched elected officials.
24区直言不讳的詹姆斯·波顿议员
Outspoken Alderman James Burton of the 24th ward
今早在商业区遭到枪击
was gunned down this morning in the financial district.
街道环卫工人一小时前发现他的
Streets and Sanitation worker found him an hour ago.
头部中枪  估计死亡时间在凌晨两点到三点之间
GSW to the head, T.O.D. between 2:00 A.M., 3:00 A.M.
根据尸斑判断
Based on lividity.
-有证人吗  -没有人来过
- Witnesses? - No one's come forward.
这地方下班后几乎没什么人  警长
Yeah, this place is really dead after hours, Sarge.
我估计没人会来
I doubt anybody was here.
衣兜都被翻了个底朝天
Pockets turned inside and out.
钱包  手表和手机都不见了
Wallet, watch, and cell phone are gone.
有挣扎的痕迹吗
Any signs of a struggle?
没有  好像是抢劫杀人
Nope, looks like a robbery gone wrong.
知道伯顿议员为什么会来这里吗
Know what Alderman Burton was doing down here?
在王冠酒吧喝酒
Drinking at the Crown Pub.
酒保说他当时和一个银行家一起
Bartender said he was with a banker,
鲁迪·芬尼根  打烊才走
Rudy Finnegan, till closing.
我们去找他聊聊
We'll go talk to him.
我听这个议员说过
I heard this alderman said
警察只在乎白人死者
cops only care about white victims.
很想告诉这个混蛋
I'd love to tell this jackass
我在加班加点
I'm working double overtime
调查杀害他自己的凶手
to help find the guy who killed him.
汉克
Hank.
你女儿能恢复真是太好了
Hey, that's great news about your daughter.
我听说她会没事
I hear she's going to be okay.
是的  医生做得很好
Yeah, doctors did a great job.
-是伯顿啊  -没错
- Burton, huh? - Yeah.
你知道他和市长关系很好吗
You know he and the mayor were very close friends.
是的  市长希望你们赶紧侦破这个案子
Yeah, the mayor would like your team to work this quick.
明白
Understood.
奥林斯基警探
Detective Olinsky.
我们想和你谈谈
We'd like a word.
怎么回事
What's this about?
别在这里说  回警局
Not here. Down at headquarters.
这很重要  埃尔
It's important, Al.
不然我们也不会来
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't.
放开我
Get off me, man.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is this about?
感谢你的到来  奥林斯基警探
Thanks for coming in, Detective Olinsky.
我为什么会在这里
So why am I here?
我们要问你几个问题
We need to ask you some questions.
-什么问题  -凯文·宾汉姆
- About? - Kevin Bingham.
他杀死了汉克·博伊特的儿子
He murdered Hank Voight's son.
他们六周前在一家超市门口
They dug his body up about six weeks ago
挖出了他的尸体
at a Super Mart construction site.
所以呢
So?
你见过这家伙吗
You meet the guy?
听着
Okay, look.
宾汉姆的身上发现了另一个人的DNA
Third party DNA was found on Bingham's body.
你的
Yours.
埃尔
Al.
你能解释一下死者
Can you explain how your hair
身上为什么会有你的头发吗
ended up on the victim?
律师
Lawyer.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十七集
我和伯顿议员一起待了两小时
I was with Alderman Burton for about two hours.
他希望我在他的分区投资一些
He wanted me to invest in some urban revitalization project
-城市复兴项目  -大半夜的
- in his ward. - At midnight?
是的  他坚持要晚饭后见面
Oh, yeah, he insisted that we meet after dinner.
他好像很需要现金
He seemed desperate for cash.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他提出可以支付百分之十五的利息
Well, he offered to pay 15% interest.
简直是市场通行利率的两倍了
That's double the market rate.
我们是朋友  但他这样说让我很紧张
We're friends, but that made me nervous.
所以我拒绝了
So I, uh, passed.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
然后我在酒吧
Then I got in my Uber
两点零一分叫车走了
at 2:01 at the bar,
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   不高兴童鞋   小萝莉
伯顿也走了
and Burton went down the street.
翻译     Lynn_宁   H小欠   圈圈
有发现什么可疑的事吗
You see anything suspicious?
没有  但是酒吧里之前有个家伙
No. There was a guy at the bar earlier.
黑人  走了进来
African-American, came in,
校对     圈圈
环顾四周几分钟
looked around for a few minutes,
什么都没点就走了
left without ordering.
能描述一下细节吗  年龄  身高
Any details on that? Age, height?
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
30不到  中等个头
Eh, late twenties, average height and build.
后期     8T
如果想起别的就联系我们  好吗
You think of anything else, give us a call, okay?
好的  谢谢你的来电
Yeah. Hey, listen, thanks for calling.
总监     圈圈
顺便  你觉得为什么
Hey, by the way, why do you think
那个内务部的人要找奥林斯基
that IAD picked up Olinsky?
我不知道
I don't know.
奥林斯基的事你不懂
With Olinsky, you may never know.
你有任何需要都可以
So anything you need, anything at all,
直接联络我
you have my private number.
我知道你和詹姆斯对我们警方有疑虑
I know you and James had doubts about our police,
但是我们在改变
but we're changing things.
博伊特警长一定会尽他所能
You'll be in good hands with Sergeant Voight here.
谢谢你  丹尼
Thank you, Denny.
-好了  -谢谢
- All right. - Thank you.
局长
Commander.
-我们很遗憾  -谢谢
- We're so sorry for your loss. - Thank you.
这是整个城市的损失
It's a loss for everyone, the entire city.
没错
It is.
很抱歉挑这个时候
Sorry to do this now,
但你丈夫的私人物品都被偷走了
but your husband's personal items were stolen.
如果你能告诉我们都是些什么  描述一下
And if you tell me what they are, if you describe them,
我们也许能找到偷走这些东西的人
we may be able to track down the offender who stole them.
你觉得这只是一起愚蠢的抢劫吗
You think this was a stupid robbery?
妈妈  这只是她的工作
Mom, she's just trying to do her job--
我丈夫是一名领导
My husband was a leader.
一个有远见的人  他将这个区改造成一个
A visionary, he was transforming this ward
有活力  蓬勃的社区
into a vibrant, bustling community.
他不是因为什么名表死的
He didn't die over some damn Rolex.
我父亲去年通过了一项条款
My father passed an ordinance last year.
经济落后地区的开发商
Uh, developers of blighted areas
五年无需支付地产税
don't have to pay property taxes for five years.
有些当地人应该并不喜欢这个条款
Guess some of the locals weren't too happy about that.
是的  他们在我们家前门抗议
Yes, they protested on our front lawn,
划我们的轮胎  进行死亡威胁
slashed our tires, made death threats.
有名字吗
Did you get any names?
区秘书记下了所有
The ward secretary kept track
恶意来电和电邮
of all the angry calls and emails.
谢谢您  夫人  先生
Thank you, ma'am, sir.
我们从议员的秘书那里拿到了
Hey, we got a list of pissed-off locals
对议员不满的人的名单  少说有50人
from the alderman's secretary. There's at least 50 names.
我们没能找到芬尼根在王冠酒吧看到的
We weren't able to get video of the male black
那个黑人男性的视频
Finnegan saw at the Crown Pub.
那议员的个人物品呢
What about the alderman's personal belongings?
他的手机没信号  信用卡也没动静
His phone has no signal, no hits on his credit cards,
而他的劳力士也还没被卖出去
and his Rolex hasn't popped up in any pawn shops yet.
我觉得你们应该知道议员的夫人正在电视上
I thought you should know the alderman's wife is on TV
表达对芝加哥警署处理黑人政治家时
expressing concern about Chicago PD's dedication
专注度的担忧
to black politicians.
这才过了多久  5小时吗
It's been like what, five hours?
她为什么追得这么紧
Why is she going so hard at this?
她聪明  想保持压力
She's smart. She wants to keep the pressure on.
好  排查当地不满人士
All right, so run the names of the angry locals.
但也不要放弃抢劫案的想法
But don't give up on this robbery angle either.
亚当
Listen, Adam.
我想让你去联系伍兹
I want you to reach out to Woods.
看看他知不知道老埃是什么情况
See if he knows what's going on with Al.
你还没和他说上话吗
You haven't talked to him?
还是联系不上
Still out of touch.
这可不太妙
Well, that's not a good sign.
那好
All right.
我从遗体上提取了外来毛发和纤维
I pulled foreign hair and fibers from the body
做了基因分析
doing the DNA analysis.
死因是头部这一枪
Cause of death, single gunshot to the head.
这是取出来的子弹
This is the recovered bullet.
这是点223口径空尖弹  来自自动步枪
It's a hollow point .223 caliber from assault rifle.
可能是一支AR-15
Probably AR-15.
进入伤很干净
Entry wound is clean.
没有烟痕和火药灼伤  或内部气蚀
No soot, powder tattooing, internal cavitation.
这么说是远程击杀
So it was fired from a distance.
对
That's right.
这么说有人从远处狙杀了议员
So someone sniped the alderman from far away
然后上前来抢了他
and then they get close to rob him.
这根本说不通
That doesn't make any sense.
没错  是说不通
Yeah, you're right. It doesn't.
除非目的就是暗杀
Unless it was a hit.
而抢劫只是想转移我们注意力
And a robbery was just to throw us off the scent, right?
多谢
Thanks.
局长
Commander.
Commander!
我发了几条短信
I sent a few texts.
我不知道你有没有收到
I don't know if they went through.
我收到了  你来干什么
No, I got them. Why are you here?
我听说内务部传唤了奥林斯基
I, uh, heard that IA picked up Olinsky.
不知道跟宾汉姆案有没有关系
Does this got something to do with Bingham?
长官  我只是想帮忙
Look, sir, I'm just trying to help.
也是想办好我的案子
Just trying to work off my case,
而博伊特看起来真的很紧张
and Voight, he seems real nervous.
我觉得这可能是个好机会
I think this could be a good opportunity.
所以如果有什么需要我做的
So if there's something you want me to do,
我随时待命
I'm ready for you.
再也不要联系我了
Don't contact me again, ever.
长官
Sir.
我有需要时  会找你的
If I need you, I will find you.
好的长官
Yes, sir.
-他拒绝了你  -非常冷淡
- He shut you down. - He was ice cold.
因为他不再需要你了
'Cause he doesn't need you anymore.
也就是说他手上奥林斯基的把柄非常要命
Which means whatever he's got on Olinsky is real.
我们检测了议员身上的外来基因
We ran the foreign DNA on the alderman's body.
匹配上了一个达利斯·布朗
It's a match to Darius Brown
正好住在伯顿的选区
who also lives in Burton's ward.
-前科  -一次伤人
- Priors? - One for assault.
半年前差点把房东打死
Beat the hell out of his landlord six months ago
因为房东想把房租翻倍
'cause he tried to double the rent.
你查到他现居地的地址了吧
Tell me you got a current address.
查到了
We do.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
门开着
All right, it's open.
-在你右侧  -好
- On your right. - Okay.
达利斯·布朗
Darius Brown!
我太吵了吗  警官
Was I too loud, Officer?
他们在宾汉姆的身上找到了你的基因
They found your DNA on Bingham's body?
是
Yeah.
你怎么说的
What'd you say?
我说我要律师  然后谈话就结束了
I said I wanted a lawyer, and the meeting was over.
有人选了吗
Anyone in mind?
有  彼得·马内蒂
Yeah, Peter Manetti.
他挺可靠
He's good.
但也很贵
Expensive, too.
十万块  一次付清
100 grand, up front.
哥们  我
Listen, man, I...
我不想开口  但是
I hate to ask, but...
我可能需要从你的应急基金里借点钱
I might need to borrow some money from your Rainy Day fund.
老埃  我把所有的钱都给孙子存信托了
Al, I put all that money in a trust fund for my grandson.
当他们挖出宾汉姆的尸体时
When they dug up Bingham's body,
我就觉着我随时会被捕  所以...
I figured I could get arrested at any minute, so.
天啊
Man.
当我发现他时  他已经死了
When I found him, he was already dead.
我不知道他是个议员
I didn't know he was an alderman.
所以你就那么碰巧大半夜在金融区
All right, so you just happened to walk up to a body
撞见了这么一具尸体
in the middle of the night in the financial district?
我正往家走
I was walking home.
听见有枪声  我就跑过来看
And I heard a gunshot, so I went to look.
我就看见这人躺在小巷里  流了血
I saw this dude in the alley, bleeding,
但他已经死了
but he was dead.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
-我就是知道  -好吧
- I just knew. - Okay.
你把他抢劫了吗
Did you rob him?
抢他
Rob him?
那也太不尊重人了
Now, that would be disrespectful.
抱歉打断一下  达利斯
Sorry to interrupt. Darius.
你看看我在你住处找到了什么
Look what I found in your apartment.
你这个时机卡得可真是太好了
Well, that was excellent timing right there
因为达利斯刚刚告诉我们
because Darius was just telling us
他没抢议员的东西
how he didn't rob the alderman.
我从没说我没抢劫他
No, I never said I didn't rob him.
我是说抢他的东西
Ah. I said robbing him
太不尊重了
would be disrespectful.
-不一样的  -天啊
- There's a difference. - Oh, my God.
你到底偷没偷他的手机和劳力士
Did you steal his phone? His Rolex?
当然了
Of course I did.
怎么  那人都死了
What? The man was dead.
又不需要知道现在几点了
Ain't like he needed to know what time it was.
但这不代表人是我杀的
But that don't mean I killed the man.
但是看起来嫌疑很大啊
No, but it looks pretty good.
除非你给我点有用的信息
And unless you tell me something helpful
不然我现在就对你提出
I'm gonna charge your ass right now
杀人指控
with murder.
好吧  我走近尸体的时候
Okay, when I was walking up to the body,
看到了一辆蓝色小轿车
I saw a blue sedan.
应该是克莱斯勒
A Chrysler, I think.
它很快就开走了
It was driving away too fast.
-你看到车里的人了吗  -没看见
- You see who was in the car? - I couldn't see.
天太黑了
It was dark.
我发誓我没杀人
Look, I swear to God I did not kill that man.
行吧
Mm-kay.
为防万一  我们得让你在这里
Well, just to be sure, we're going to keep you here
多待一会儿  所以你就老实待着吧
for a little while, so get comfortable.
不是吧
C'mon.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah, really.
老大  这是好消息
So, boss, this is the good news.
芝加哥市内总共只有5260辆蓝色克莱斯勒轿车
There's only 5,260 blue Chrysler sedans in the city of Chicago.
好  查一下那些注册在54号大街住户名下的
All right, run the ones registered to people living in the 54th.
查过了  还剩下832辆
Did that. It narrowed it down to 832.
也没办法
Huh. It is what it is.
查一下车主姓名  看看能查到什么
Run the names, see what you find.
大家伙  来看看这个
Hey, guys, check this out.
这是波顿议员手机上的一条语音留言
This is a voicemail from Alderman Burton's phone.
你这个贪婪投机的伪君子
You are a greedy, opportunistic hypocrite
你该去死
and deserve to die.
这是昨晚十一点前留下的
That was left last night just before 11:00 p.m.,
电话是从道格拉斯公园餐馆的
and the call came from a pay phone
一个公用电话打来的
at a Douglas Park diner.
叫上厄普顿  去查查看
Grab Upton. Check it out.
就是这里
This is the place.
没有监控摄像
No security cameras.
抱歉  先生
Excuse me, sir.
你是这里的老板吗
Are you the owner of this place?
-对  -我是厄普顿警探
- I am. - I'm Detective Upton.
这位是霍斯特德警探
This is Detective Halstead.
我们在调查一起凶杀案
We're investigating a homicide.
你昨晚关门之前有没有看到
Did you see somebody use that pay phone last night
有人用了那部公用电话
just before closing time?
没看到
Uh, can't say that I did.
那你能不能帮我们听段录音
Will you take a listen to something for us?
你这个贪婪
You are a greedy,
投机的伪君子
opportunistic hypocrite
你该去死
and deserve to die.
你认得这个声音吗
You recognize that voice?
不认识
Can't say that I do.
好吧
Right.
谢谢您的帮助
Well, thank you for your time.
-怎么了  -我看到了一只老鼠
- What? - I just saw a rat.
看来有只老鼠跑进厨房了
Looks like it ran right into the kitchen.
俗话说得好啊  只要看到一只老鼠
You know what they say, when there's one rat,
那就说明还有更多
there's always more.
是啊  那我们得上报给
Yeah, and then we got to call it in
卫生部门了
to the Health Department.
再给我听听那段录音
Uh, let me listen to that message again.
说不定这次能想起什么来
Maybe something will click this time.
这就对了嘛
I like where your head's at.
你这个贪婪投机的伪君子
You are a greedy, opportunistic hypocrite
你该去死
and deserve to die.
听起来有点像科尔曼·路易斯
Kind of sounds like Coleman Lewis.
他是这里的常客
He's a regular.
很关心邻里的大小事
Very passionate about the neighborhood.
希望可以保持现有的环境
Wants to keep things the way they are.
谢谢
Thank you.
记得找人来灭鼠
Make sure you call that exterminator.
对  那当然是我
Yeah, you better believe that was me.
在我看来  你这是承认
Okay, sounds like you admit
威胁要谋杀波顿议员了
to threatening to kill Alderman Burton to me.
我说的是他该死
I said he deserved to die.
我不认为这话有错
And I stand by that.
-但我没杀他  -好吧
- But I didn't kill him. - Okay, well,
教授  我们只想知道剩下的故事
Professor, we just want to hear the rest of the story.
所以你是个拥有持枪许可的音乐教授
So you are a music professor with a gun permit?
还被抓到破坏车辆
You got pinched for vandalizing a car?
有个开发商把他的新雷克萨斯
Some developer parks his brand new Lexus
停在了我的车道上
in my driveway.
堵了我整整两个小时
Blocks me in for two hours.
他根本不尊重我
He has no regard whatsoever for me
也不尊重这栋公寓楼里的其他住户
or any of the residents in my apartment building.
你们告诉我  你们真的相信
Now, you guys tell me, do you really believe
我是杀害波顿的真凶
that I'm the one that killed Burton?
我昨晚压根都不在芝加哥
I wasn't even in town last night.
那你在哪里
Where were you?
我开车去了匹兹堡
I was driving to Pittsburgh.
匹兹堡  去那儿干啥
Pittsburgh? What's in Pittsburgh?
去卡耐基梅隆大学的珍稀图书馆
The rare books library at Carnegie Mellon.
那里有一本福音手稿我想看
There was a gospel manuscript I wanted to see.
波顿想要毁掉低音蓝调俱乐部
Burton was gonna demolish the Low Note Blues Club,
你们敢信吗
if you can believe that.
那可是全国最佳标志性的演奏会场之一
All right? It is one of the most iconic venues
很多伟大的音乐家都在那里演出过
in this country, and the greatest people played there.
所以你没杀人
Okay, so you didn't do it.
那谁杀的
Who did?
那谁知道
Who knows?
波顿和他儿子都很黑
Burton and his son play dirty.
有很多人都对他们很不满
Plenty of people that are angry with them.
他儿子  阿瑟吗  他干什么了
His son, Arthur? What does he have to do with anything?
他是低音项目的开发商
He's the developer on the Low Note project.
-这我倒是不知道  -没错
- That I didn't know. - Oh, yeah, well.
老爹给儿子找的好差事呗
Daddy gave junior a plum prize.
甚至重新规划  好让他的工作更轻松
Even re-zoned things to make it nice and easy for him.
你说他们很黑  你有证据吗
You said they were dirty. I mean, you got any proof?
我亲眼见到阿瑟走进了路边酒吧
I've seen Arthur go into the Roadside Bar,
-应该有两三次吧  -那又如何
- two, maybe three times. - So?
那是个帮派聚集地
It's a gang hangout.
路边酒吧吗  对啊
The Roadside Bar? Yeah.
我去那儿喝过酒
I've stopped in there for a drink.
在我的一个工程附近
It's near a project of mine.
-低音  -对
- The Low Note? - That's the one.
那是你父亲为了你重新规划的
Which your father had re-zoned for you.
你觉得我受到优待了吗
You think I got special favors?
告诉你  没人想要低音
Let me tell you, nobody wanted the Low Note.
瘾君子在大厅里开枪混战
Junkies shoot up in the lobby over there.
你到底是什么意思
What are you getting at anyway?
你和你父亲有没有和那个工程
Did you and your father have any side deals
相关的附带交易
related to that project?
阿瑟  如果你和当地帮派有关
Listen, Arthur, if you're involved with a local gang--
那是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
和当地帮派有关
Involved with a local gang?
你是在暗示我儿子
Are you suggesting that my son,
我受过常春藤联盟教育的儿子是黑帮成员吗
my Ivy League-educated son, is a gangbanger?
不  女士  我只是想弄清
No, ma'am, I'm just trying to figure out
谁杀了你的丈夫
who killed your husband.
而现在我们没有很多线索
And right now we don't have a whole lot of leads,
所以我对你们家族生意了解得越多
so the more I know about your family's business
会越利于破案
dealings the better.
我对你就快失去信任了  博伊特警长
I'm quickly losing faith in you, Sergeant Voight.
也许我该让丹尼·伍兹知道
Maybe I should let Denny Woods know
比起找出杀害我丈夫的凶手
that you're more focused on tearing my family down
你更专注于毁掉我的家庭
than finding my husband's killer.
请你走吧
We're done here.
普拉特  你知道老埃怎么了吗
Platt, do you know what's going on with Al?
和宾汉姆的尸体有关吗
Does it have to do with Bingham's body?
-这事别来问我  -安东尼奥
- I am not the guy to ask. - Hey, Antonio.
-科尔曼·路易斯的不在场证明查了吗  -查了
- Coleman Lewis' alibi check out? - Yeah, sure does.
那天早些时候他在卡内基梅隆
He was at Carnegie Mellon checking out
查阅珍藏版书籍
rare books early that morning.
时间线证明不是很完美  但很紧凑
Timeline isn't perfect, but it's pretty tight.
鉴证科会计调查了
And we have a forensic accountant looking
波顿家庭的财务情况
into Burton family finances.
好  我看看你查到了什么
All right, good. Let me know what you find.
-好  -我是博伊特
- Okay. - Voight.
等等
Hold on.
好
Yeah.
我们就去
We'll be right there.
阿瑟·波顿应该在3点和承包商在这见面的
Arthur Burton was supposed to meet a contractor here at 3:00.
承包商迟到了
Contractor was late.
到的时候发现他死了
Found him dead when he arrived.
-有目击者吗  -还没有
- Any witnesses? - None so far.
一枪击中头部  和他父亲一样
Single shot to the head, just like his father.
谢谢  诺威克
Thanks, Novick.
这和什么瑜伽工作室  公寓
Man, this isn't about yoga studios or condos
或捣毁黑文化都没关系
or destroying black culture.
我们是站在海洛因大道的中心
We're standing in the middle of the heroin highway.
这事关毒品
This is about drugs.
这个老布鲁斯俱乐部会被拆掉
This old blues club gets torn down,
公寓建起来
condos put up,
这会搞砸他们整个交易模式
it would screw up their whole business model.
谢谢  女士
Thank you, ma'am.
我没改变过他的房间
I never changed his room.
自从他离开去上大学后就没变过
Not since the day he left for college.
节哀
I'm so sorry.
我们以亚瑟王给他起的名字
We named him after King Arthur.
抱歉  但我要问你几个问题
I apologize, but I need to ask you about some things.
听说过海洛因大道吗
Have you ever heard of the heroin highway?
那是郊区的人买毒品的地方
That's where folks from the suburbs buys drugs.
在一端付钱  在另一端拿货
Pay on one end, pick up the product on the other.
很快就可以回家
Back home in no time.
我丈夫和我在帮派和毒品的环境下长大
My husband and I grew up with gangs, with drugs.
我近距离也亲历过暴力和伤痛
I've seen the violence and the pain up close and personal.
我还是孩子时就因为这种事失去了妹妹
I lost my sister to all that nonsense when I was just a kid.
我知道那是怎么运转的
Yeah, I know how it works.
我知道规则
I know the rules.
你觉得阿瑟知道吗
Do you think Arthur knew the rules?
他知道帮派不支持他的工程
He knew the gang wasn't in favor of the project.
但詹姆斯和阿瑟告诉过我他们解决了
But James and Arthur told me they worked it out.
达成了一个协议
Came to some sort of an arrangement.
你知道是什么协议吗
Do you know what that was?
他们没说细节
No, they didn't go into details.
他们只是说解决问题了
They just said they took care of the problem.
你丈夫和儿子建的公司
Look, the LLC your husband and son formed
付了几笔现金给一个叫林肯·阿万佐诺的人
made several cash payments to a guy named Lincoln Avanzano.
但这个人好像不存在
But he doesn't seem to exist.
你觉得这是他们解决问题的方法吗
You think that's how they handled the problem?
给帮派钱吗
Paid off the gang?
有可能
It's possible.
你觉得会是哪个帮派
And what gang do you think it would be?
西区门徒
The Westside Disciples.
不知道波顿议员或他的孩子
Don't know Alderman Burton or his kid.
他们现在都死了
Well, they're both dead now.
太糟了
That's too bad.
据说他们之前试着和西区门徒
Word is, they tried to work a deal
进行一个交易
with the Westside Disciples.
那是你的帮派
That's your gang.
-是吗  -给你钱
- Is that right? - Gave you cash
好让你不去干预他们的建筑工程
so you wouldn't interfere with their construction project.
这我可不知道
Don't know nothing about that.
很难相信
That's hard to believe.
你控制海洛因大道
I mean, you control the heroin highway.
不是整条大道
Not all of it.
低音俱乐部所在的那块呢
The part where the Low Note Club is?
那儿有很多帮派
There's a lot of gangs involved in there.
可能吧
Yeah, that may be.
但你才是说了算的人
But you're the one calling the shots.
告诉你我怎么想的  拉玛
I'll tell you what I think, Lamar.
我猜波顿过来找你谈生意
See, I think the Burtons came to you with a deal.
你很喜欢  就接受了
You liked it. You accepted it.
但他们拿不出所有的钱
But they couldn't come up with all the cash,
然后你就不爽了
and, well, you didn't like that.
所以就干掉了他们
So you popped them.
而且在此过程中
And in the process
你把整个建筑交易都扼杀了
you killed that whole construction deal.
因为不会有人想在那里盖房子
'Cause no one's gonna want to build there.
现在不想
Not now.
聊完了吗
We done?
反正我说够了
'Cause I'm done talking.
好啊
That's fine.
因为你已经告诉我我需要知道的一切了
'Cause you already told me everything I need to know.
考虑过你的未来吗
Have you thought about your future?
你马上就要退休  拿到丰厚的退休金了
You are damn close to a fat pension.
和家人一起度过  在佛罗里达的船上过慵懒的日子
Spending time with your family, lazy days on a boat in Florida.
我不想看你在这么多年兢兢业业的奉献之后
I'd hate to see you lose all that
连这都没有了
after years of dedicated service.
我为什么会拿不到我的退休金
Is there a reason I would?
内务部跟我说了宾汉姆一案
IAD filled me in on the Bingham investigation.
除了DNA匹配之外
Besides the DNA match,
他们有目击者看到你和一个年轻女子
they have a witness who saw you and a young woman
出现在建筑工地的超市
at the Super Mart construction site,
就在我们找到宾汉姆尸体的地方
same place we recovered Bingham's body.
你被卷到这些事情里的唯一原因
And the only reason you were involved in any of this
就是博伊特
is because of Voight.
你对宾汉姆没有什么企图
You had no ax to grind with that man Bingham.
但是你合作的话...
But you cooperate...
你获得全部豁免权
You get full immunity.
继续干你的工作
You stay on the job.
领你的全额退休金
Keep your full pension.
我无话可说
I got nothing to say.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
你保护博伊特是因为你的原则
See, you're protecting Voight because that's your code.
但你是最后一个了
But you're the last of a breed.
忠诚高于一切
Loyalty above all else.
我问你
Let me ask you something.
你觉得博伊特会担下责任来保护你吗
You think Voight would fall on his sword to protect you?
不会的  他不会那么做的
Nah. He wouldn't.
我了解博伊特
I know Voight.
我也了解他
I do, too.
我们从阿瑟·波顿的枪击案调出了视频监控
We pulled video surveillance from Arthur Burton's shooting.
蓝色的克莱斯勒轿车
Blue Chrysler sedan.
就像那个从犯罪现场逃走的劳力士小偷说的
Just like the Rolex thief said sped away from the crime scene.
我们查了车牌  发布了通缉
We ran the plates, and we put out a BOLO.
车是注册在基翁·沃尔特斯名下的
The car is registered to a Keon Walters.
我们正在查他的家庭住址
We're trying to find his home address.
车是在亚契街兰登市场后面发现的
Car was just spotted behind Landon's Market on Archer.
好  现在就去那边
All right, get over there now.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
我们谈谈
Let's talk.
你有什么消息吗
You hear anything else?
没  什么都没有
No, nothing.
伍兹呢  你和他聊过了吗
What about Woods? You talk to him?
聊过了
I did.
我猜你已经知道了
I'm guessing you already know that.
他说什么了
What did he say?
他说他有目击者看到我和一个女人
Well, he claims he's got a witness that saw me and a woman
在宾汉姆埋葬点附近出现
near Bingham's burial site
18个月前
18 months ago.
关于这个女人他还说了什么吗
He say anything more about this woman?
20来岁
Twenties.
深色头发
Dark hair.
他早晚会查出她是谁的
It's only a matter of time before he figures out who it is.
也有可能是诈我们
Might be a bluff.
想让我们乱了阵脚  忙中出错
You know, wants us to panic, make mistakes.
我再查查
I'll do some digging.
司机上车了
Driver's getting in the car.
好  我们看到了  没看到有乘客
Yep, we got eyes. No passenger visible.
-你准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
基翁·沃尔特斯  下车
Keon Walters! Get out of the car!
下车
Out of the car!
熄火
Turn off the car!
熄火  下车
Turn the car off and get out of the car!
5021G紧急情况
5021 George emergency.
我们在追一辆蓝色克莱斯勒汽车
We're in pursuit of a blue Chrysler
在利维街向北逃离  刚通过13号大街
fleeing northbound on Levy, just past 13th street.
伊利诺伊车牌  65GI8C
Illinois tag 65 George Ida 8 Charlie.
警察  举起手来
Police! Show me your hands.
把手放到我能看到的地方
Let me see your hands!
把手放到窗户上  快点
Put your hands on the glass. Do it now!
下车  把你的手放在车顶
Get out of the car. Put your hands on the roof.
别动
Don't move.
AR-15突击步枪
AR-15 assault rifle.
就是它
Bingo.
走
Let's go.
基翁·沃尔特斯  21岁  住菲尔莫尔街907号
Keon Walters, age 21, he lives at 907 Fillmore.
-没有前科  -他不在我们系统里
- No priors. - He's not in our system.
也不在黑帮成员数据库里
He's not in the gang database either.
-弹道  -匹配
- Ballistics? - It's a match.
基翁车里的步枪就是两件谋杀案中的凶器
The rifle in Keon's trunk was used in both murders.
指纹
Prints?
没有  这正是奇怪的地方
No, and this is where it gets weird.
我们找了那个银行家  芬尼根
We reached out to the banker, Finnegan.
他说他很确定不是基翁
He said he's certain Keon's not the guy
在案发当晚在酒吧外面踩点
he saw scoping out the bar the night of the murder.
是的  我们搜了他的车  所有物  没有手机
Yeah, we searched his car, belongings. No phone.
除了步枪之外我们只找到
Only things we found other than the rifle
一双12码的靴子和
were a pair of size 12 boots
一件特大号的冬季外套
and an extra-large winter jacket.
-好  你跟我来  -12码
- All right, me and you. - Size 12?
那不可能是基翁的  他也就是个一米六八
Those kicks can't be Keon's. Kid's barely 5'6".
听起来那孩子可能有个共犯
Sounds like the kid might have a partner.
好了  给他做个面部识别
All right, run him through facial rec online.
看看能不能找到他的搭档
See if you can find who he hangs with.
一个
One potato.
两个
Two potato.
我们在你车里找到的步枪
Rifle we found in your trunk.
就是杀死波顿议员和他儿子的凶器
It's the same weapon used to kill alderman Burton and his son.
我没杀过人
I didn't kill no one.
好
Okay.
那你告诉我
So tell me.
那步枪是怎么到你车里的
How'd the rifle end up in your trunk?
你能告诉我吗
Can you tell me that?
我们知道你有个共犯
We know you got a partner.
好了  你看起来像是个好孩子
C'mon. You seem like a pretty good kid.
没有逮捕记录  没参加帮派
No arrests, no gang affiliations.
所以我们猜
That's why we're guessing
不是你开的枪
you're not the one doing the shooting.
也就是说你有机会做个交易
Which means you have a chance to cut yourself a deal.
你只需要...
All you got to do...
告诉我们另一个人是谁
Give us who you're working with.
我无话可说
I got nothing to say.
兄弟  我知道这种感觉很好
Look, bro, I know it feels good.
守口如瓶  忠诚
Keep your mouth shut. Be loyal.
但那很傻
But it's stupid.
太蠢了
It's stupid.
因为
'Cause...
最后要服刑的是你
You're the one who's gonna end up doing the time.
不是你兄弟
Not your buddy.
你
You.
你明白吗
You understand?
监狱生活不是闹着玩的  兄弟
And life in prison is no joke, bro.
是终生的
It's forever.
每一天
Every day.
每一晚
Every night.
你余生都要这样
For the rest of your existence.
希望吃饭时跟你有眼神接触的哥们
Hoping some dude you made eye contact with at breakfast
不会往你脖子上扎一刀
doesn't stick a shiv in your neck.
做人聪明点
Be smart.
事关你的人生  基翁
This is your life, Keon.
没有人值得你做这样的牺牲  相信我
There's nobody worth sacrificing that for, believe me.
没有人
Nobody.
所以
So.
我没什么可说的
I got nothing to say.
血液学基金会
这张照片哪里来的
Where'd you get this photo?
网上  面部识别
Online. Facial recognition.
-基翁有麻烦了吗  -是的
- Is Keon in trouble? - Yeah.
我们认为他跟议员和他儿子的谋杀案有关
We think he's involved in the murder of an alderman and his son.
不可能  肯定不是基翁
No way. Couldn't be Keon.
-不是吗  -你确定吗
- No? - You sure?
你跟他很熟吗
Know him pretty well?
我们是高中时认识的
We met in high school.
他每隔几个月来医院都会来见我
I see him every few months when he comes to the hospital.
-他有镰状细胞性贫血  -是的
- He's got sickle cell anemia. - Oh, uh, yeah.
你知道他是不是黑帮的人吗
Do you know if he's in a gang?
不是  他人很好
No, he's a nice guy.
我们出去约会过几次
We went on a couple of dates.
我跟你说  他不会杀人
I'm telling you he's not killer.
好的  如果你想帮他  我觉得你想的
Okay, well, if you want to help him and I think you do,
就把你知道的所有事都告诉我们
just tell us everything you know.
-我说  我发誓  -他的朋友呢
- I am. I swear. - What about his friends?
认识他在黑帮的朋友吗
Any of them in gangs that you know of?
不认识
No.
但他的堂兄肯定是黑帮的
But I'm pretty sure his cousin is.
他有时候会陪基翁来看病
He comes to Keon's appointments sometimes.
好的  他堂兄叫什么
Okay, what's his cousin's name?
基翁叫他LJ  我不知道他的真名
Keon calls him LJ. I don't know his real name.
可能访客登记表上会有
It's probably in the visitors' log somewhere.
-好的  -谢谢你
- Noted. - Thank you.
不如你跟我们说说你堂兄吧
Why don't you tell us about your cousin...
拉玛·詹金斯
Lamar Jenkins.
LJ
LJ?
是的  你很熟
Yeah, you know big cuz.
他负责西区门徒
Runs the Westside Disciples.
还有所有海洛因大道的事
And everything on the heroin highway.
这些我们都知道了
That much we do know.
真正杀人的是拉玛  对吗
Lamar is the one who actually did the murders, right?
不是他就是你  基翁
It's either him or you, Keon.
不知道你在说什么
Don't know what you're talking about.
不管我们逼得多紧  这孩子都不会松口
This kid's not gonna crack no matter how hard we push.
不会  我们会撬开他的嘴
Nah, we'll break him.
只需要找到他的弱点
Just got to find his weakness.
每个人都有一个极限  老埃
Everybody's got a breaking point, Al.
不管你有多坚强
No matter how strong you are.
不是所有人都一样
Well, not everyone.
我们找不到拉玛的住址
We can't find a home address for Lamar.
我跟你说的那个酒吧你查了吗
You check out that bar I told you about?
查了  他不在  巡逻车一小时前去过
Yeah, he's not there. Patrol stopped by an hour ago.
那地方好像关门了
The place looks shut down.
我们抓了他堂弟之后
You know, he's probably been on the run
他可能就跑路了
ever since we pinched his cousin.
你可能是对的
You're probably right.
看来我们得换个方式了
Guess we have to come up with a different approach.
他的外套应该还在我们这里吧
I assume we still got his coat.
你继续嘴硬吧  基翁
You keep playing tough guy, Keon,
时间不多了
the clock is gonna run out.
刚跟助理检察官谈过  叫我放了他
Just talked to the ASA. Told me to kick him free.
什么  真的吗
What? You serious?
他不肯说  我们也没足够的证据起诉他
He ain't talking and we don't have enough to charge him.
走吧  你可以去楼下拿东西了
Come on. You can grab your stuff downstairs.
待在本市别出去  这还没完
Stay in town. This ain't over.
放好了吗
You all set?
好了  我在他外套里放了追踪器和窃听器
Yeah, I put a tracker and mic in his coat.
他要出来了  杰
He's coming out, Jay.
收到  警长  我们就位了
Copy that, Sarge. We're in position.
这孩子可能知道我们的计划
This kid might be on to us.
他已经走了二十分钟了
He's been walking for 20 minutes.
也许他只是想离警局远一点
Yeah, maybe he just wanted some distance from the station.
也许吧
Maybe.
一站式食品店
他刚刚走进一家小超市
He just went in to a mini-mart.
他在打电话  肯定刚买了个一次性手机
He's dialing. He must have bought a burner.
我是基翁  过来接我
Yo, it's Keon. Come get me.
我在圣伊格内修斯附近的罗斯福街
I'm on Roosevelt near Saint Ignatius.
是的
Yeah.
跟拉玛说让他就待在河谷
And tell Lamar to stay in Riverdale.
警察在找他
The police are looking for him.
好的
All right.
警长  拉玛在河谷
Sarge, Lamar's in Riverdale.
松树街290号有一座门徒帮的房子
There's a Disciples house at 290 Pine Street.
你跟厄普顿把基翁带回来  马上
You and Upton scoop up Keon. Now.
我们会把拉玛拿下
We'll take down Lamar.
-收到  -好的
- Copy. - All right.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
手都举起来  出来
Put your hands in the air. Out!
-我上楼  -好的
- Got the stairs. - Okay.
手举起来
Put your hands up.
请你离刀远一点  女士
I want you to take a step back from that knife, ma'am.
楼上安全
Upstairs clear.
拉玛·詹金斯在哪里
Where's Lamar Jenkins?
这里没有拉玛的影子
There's no sign of Lamar in here.
你听到了吗
You hear that?
跑
Run.
-这边归我  -好的  去吧
- I got this side. - All right, go ahead.
去看看
Check it out.
-你准备好了吗  -动手  动手
- You ready? - Go, go.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
把头盔拿下来
Take the helmet off.
肯定是个藏匿点
Must be a stash house.
这里至少有20万
There's got to be at least 200 Gs here.
这是藏匿点吗
Is this a stash house?
看起来是的
Yeah, it looks that way.
阿特沃特和鲁塞克正在羁押拉玛去局里
Atwater and Ruzek are transporting Lamar back to the District.
好
All right, good.
清点一下  登记为证据
All right, clear it out. Log it into evidence.
这是你唯一的机会  拉玛
This is your one and only shot, Lamar.
你找错人了
You got the wrong man.
我们找到武器了
We have the weapon.
还有你堂弟基翁
And we got your cousin, Keon.
有他的音频指正你是枪手
He's on audio referring to you as the shooter.
那是我打篮球时候的昵称
That's my nickname. From when I played basketball.
我们只要跟基翁达成协议就行了
All we had to do was offer Keon a deal, bro.
随便你们
Offer all you want.
基翁很老派  他不会开口的
Keon? He's old school. He won't talk.
你们都别做梦了
So y'all can kiss my ass.
谢谢
Thanks.
刚问了化验室
All right, just talked to the lab.
拉玛的指纹不在车上
Lamar's prints weren't on the car.
芬尼根呢
All right, what about Finnegan?
他能明确指认吗
He able to make a positive ID?
芬尼根只是说他无法判断是不是他
All Finnegan said that he can't tell if it was the guy or not.
说实话  我觉得他是不想
Honestly to me it sounds like he didn't want
掺和帮派的事
to get involve with the gang stuff.
逮捕的证据还是足够的
We still have enough to arrest.
但我们没有足够证据给他定罪
Maybe. We sure as hell don't have enough to convict.
唯一真正的机会是策反基翁
Our only real shot is to flip Keon.
而他拒绝
Who refuses to flip.
我们因为两起谋杀案逮捕了拉玛
Well, we arrested Lamar for both murders.
我跟你说
I'll tell you this.
你堂兄可不想坐牢
Cuz ain't excited about doing no time.
-什么意思  -意思是他开口了
- What's that mean? - That means that he talkin'.
他开口了  他把你放弃了
He is talkin'. Man, that boy gave you up.
他说你是真正开枪的人
He said you the real trigger man.
是真的吗
Is that true?
是的
Yeah.
是我
Yeah, it was me.
我一个人干的
I did it on my own.
不要那样
Don't do that.
不要为他背这个锅
Don't eat this for him.
兄弟  你...
C'mon, bro, you...
他应该是你的家人
He's supposed to be your family.
他在钓你的妹子
He working your girl.
你不知道罗谢尔的事吗
Ah, you didn't know about Rochelle?
-她不是我的妹子  -拜托
- She ain't my girl. - C'mon, man.
你不用那样  我们知道你喜欢她
You don't got to do that, man. We know you like her.
我们可以通过你的社交媒体看出来
I mean, we could tell by your social media.
你很喜欢她
You like her a lot.
你看我们在她的主页上发现了什么
Look what we found on her Facebook page.
看来他们在一起玩
Looks like they've been hanging out.
我们本来都不想给你看这个
We didn't even want to show you those.
你如果进监狱了会怎样
What happens when you go to jail, man?
你堂兄和罗谢尔
And your cousin, Rochelle, they
他们就不止一起玩了
start doing more than hanging out.
那个婊子就给拉玛吧
Man, Lamar can have this bitch.
我不会开口的
I ain't talking.
这家伙很忠诚
This guy's loyal.
我们只是还没找到他的极限点
We just haven't found his breaking point.
以前我有个搭档  他的孩子有镰状细胞病
I had a partner way back. His kid had sickle cell.
很痛苦的慢性疼痛
Terrible chronic pain.
基翁  听着
All right, Keon, listen.
我们正式起诉你之前
Before we officially charge you
想先跟你说清楚几件事
just want to go over a few things.
你会去库克县  所以医疗有限
You're gonna be in Cook County so medical care is limited.
-但我有镰状细胞病  -我知道
- But I have sickle cell. - Yeah, I know.
所以我才来找你
That's why I'm here. Okay?
这张表说明了医疗情况
This form outlines the medical care.
这里  在底部签字
Here, just sign here at the bottom.
说明你拿到过复印件
All it says is that you received a copy.
我每几个月就发病
Man, I freak out every few months.
他们会送我去医院  对吧
I mean, they're gonna take me to the hospital, right?
-不  你是在监狱里  -对
- No. You're in lockup. - Yeah.
-真的那么痛苦吗  -是的
- Is the pain really that bad? - Yes!
那你可以吃点阿司匹林或布洛芬
Well, you can get some aspirin or ibuprofen.
-对  -不  我需要静脉注射杜冷丁
- Yeah. - No, I need IV Demerol.
-对  -那惨了
- Right. - Oh, man.
吃阿司匹林不管用
Like, aspirin don't do nothing.
只有杜冷丁能止痛
Demerol's the only thing that stops the pain.
-我需要杜冷丁  -好吧
- Like, I need it. - Okay.
听着
Look, listen.
你在监狱是不会得到二级毒品的
You're not gonna get a Schedule II narcotic in prison.
想都别想
There's no way.
天啊
Oh, man.
我肯定能想个办法钻钻空子
I'm sure I can figure out a way to skirt the rules.
但你得合作
But you got to play ball.
是我开的车
I drove the car.
行了吗  我开的车
All right? I drove the car.
但我没做别的  我发誓
But it's all I did. I swear.
我绝不会开枪杀人
Look, man, I ain't never shoot nobody.
都是拉玛干的
That was all Lamar.
我发誓
I swear to God.
找人问了
Talked to some sources.
目击者是真的
The witness is real.
内务部怎么找到这个这家伙的
How did Internal Affairs find this guy?
他们打了伍兹设的举报热线
They called that tip line Woods set up.
五千块奖金
$5,000 reward.
找艾琳通通气
You know, it's probably a good idea
或许是个好主意
to get Erin on the same page.
把我们的说辞讲清楚
You know...get our stories straight.
不  还是别了
No. Not so sure about that.
我们会度过这关的
We'll get through this.
你也说了  每个人都有极限点
But like you said, everyone's got a breaking point.
基翁的是杜冷丁
Keon's was Demerol.
你的是艾琳
Yours is Erin.
你的呢  老埃
What's yours, Al?